Collin Paradis

912 West Street, Ludlow, M.A 413-523-2103 CollinParadis7@gmail.com

Highly motivated college graduate with a double major in Computer Information Technology (C.I.T) and Marketing with experience in website design and Information Technology. Enthusiastic about being a part of a team that provides I.T. solutions to an organization.

Education

Elms College Chicopee, MA
Bachelors of Arts in Computer Information Technology & Bachelors of Arts in Marketing December 2018
Minor in Management GPA: 3.74

- NSF STEM Scholarship
- Manga Cum Laude

Tech FoundrySpringfield, MAA fourteen-week comprehensive I.T. career development program that focuses on
building the skills necessary to perform entry-level technical services.Exp. June 2019

- Learned how to perform hardware and software troubleshooting for Windows-based system.
- Able to resolve common networking issues at the operating system level.

Skills

Programming Languages
Operating Systems
Software

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Ajax, C#, Java Windows, Windows Server, MacOS, Linux Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere

Experience

Freelance Web Designer Salon Bocage, River Valley Rugby

Chicopee, MA January 2019- Present

- Generate and design a website based on the business owners needs and the concepts that they want portrayed.
- Maintain website by updating content, implementing new technology and monitoring performance.

Elms College Chicopee, MA Technical Support Specialist Intern August 2018 - December 2018

- Troubleshooted issues that faculty and students encounter including problems with performance, software, and peripherals.
- Utilized remote sessions to perform imaging of new computers and installation of software.
- Performed repairs on broken computers to make them functional again.

Elms College Chicopee, MA
Web Designer Intern

• Collaborated in a team to produce websites using HTML5, WordPress, and April 2017 - August 2017

April 2017 - August 2017

- Collaborated in a team to produce websites using HTML5, WordPress, and Wix that are standard compliant, SEO optimized, and multi-device. Compatible.
- Performed front-end development for websites to improve functionality and user experience using HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Managed, maintained and updated existing websites for clients.

Volunteer Activities

Elms College Tech Committee, *Member* C.I.T Computer Lab Monitor, Volunteer

August 2017 - December 2018 January 2016 - December 2018